Guide to the UE Research Department Personnel Papers, 1937-2001 UE.10.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Lyle Dowling, 1938-1942; 10.1.1.
  - Labor Management, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Labor Productivities, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Labor Reporter, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Labor's Non-Partisan Leauge, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Land, Emory S., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Legislative Bulletin, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Lipper, Ruth, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Lynching, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Lyon, Peter, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Marles, James J., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Michigan - Office of Production Management, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - National Industrial Conference Board - Charts, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - National Lawyers Guild, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Negro Discrimination, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - New Masses, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - New Union Press, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - News Release, October 1942 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - News Release, November 1942 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Newspapers, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Office of War Information, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Oldan, Raul, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Oliver, Eli, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - O'Neal, Edward, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Oneida Paper Products, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Palmer, C.H., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Parity, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Parsons, Talcott, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Pegler, Westbrook, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Perlis, Leo, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Peterson, V., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Poll Tax, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Pollock, Thomas Clark, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Post War, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Press Lists, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Press Releases, January - April 1942 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Press Releases, June 1942 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Press Releases, July 1942 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Press Releases, August 1942 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Press Releases, September 1942 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Press Releases, October 1942 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Press Releases, December 1942 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Press Releases, Time and Half and Double Time, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Press Releases, Walker Turner Decision, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Profits, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Public Affairs Committee, Inc., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Public Relations Office, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Puerto Rico, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Rabaut, Louis, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Racial Discrimination, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Radio Industry, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Randau, Carl, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Rationing, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Raw Materials, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Read, Mary, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Readers Digest, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Remington Rand Inc., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Research Directors, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Richberg, Donald, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Romeike Press Agency, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Rosenblatt, Maurice, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Rosenblatt, Maurice, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Rosenblatt, Maurice, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Rosenblatt, Maurice, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Rosenblatt, Maurice, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Rubber, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Russian War Relief, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Sabath, Adolph, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Sacher, Harry, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Sanborn Studios, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Santo, John, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Sario, Jack, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Sarti, Louis, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Sarvis, David, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Sayres, Michael, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Scalese, George, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Scherer, Marcel, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Schillinger, Joseph, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Schneiderman, Rose, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Schubert, Jack, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Scripps-Howard, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Scott, Bertha M., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Scott, Janet, 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Scovill, William, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Selective Service Act, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Seldes, George, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Sentinel (The), 1942 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Sioux City Journal, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Smith, Gerald, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Soloman, Aaron, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Spain, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Squier, George, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - St. Louis Post-Dispatch, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Stalin, Joseph, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Stavrianos, L.S., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Steelman, John, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Stibel, Jule, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Strikes, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Talon, Inc., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Tax Bill, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Taylor, Eva, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Taylor, Everett, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Teachers Union, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Technocracy, Inc., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Technology, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Teitelbaum, Bernice, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Teleradio, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Temporary National Economic Committee, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Tenerowicz, Rudolph, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Third Party, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Thompson, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Thurman, Arnold, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Time Inc. - Minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Time Inc. - Minutes, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tobenkin, Paul, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tobin, Daniel J., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tolan Bill, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Tomas, R.J., 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Towsen, Gus, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Trade Union service, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Training, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - UE- Appel, Gertrude, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - UE- Carey, James B. Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - UE- Carey, James B. Miscellaneous, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - UE- Carey, James B. Statements and Speeches, 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - UE- Chambers, Bill, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - UE- Chapman, Bill, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - UE- Conference Board, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - UE- Convention, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - UE- Convention Hotel Carter, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - UE- Convention Resolutions, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - UE- Decavitch, Victor, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - UE- Demaio, Ernest, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - UE- Dermody, Joseph, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - UE- District 4 Publication, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - UE- Emergency Plan, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - UE- Emspak, Julius, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - UE- Fitzpatrick, Michael, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - UE- Frazier, James, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - UE- Gardner, Fred, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - UE- Geller, Nat, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - UE- General Officers, 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - UE- General Officers Recommendations, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - UE- General Officers Statements, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - UE- Gojack, John T., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - UE- Gould, Norma, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - UE- Hammer, Edith, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - UE- Harley, Hugh, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - UE- Horie, Jean, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - UE- Interoffice Communications, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - UE- Jandreau, Leo, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - UE- Legislative Bulletin, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - UE- Legislative Miscellaneous, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - UE- Lewin, Leonard, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - UE- Linsley, Richard, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - UE- Local 425, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - UE- Local 426, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - UE- Local 430, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - UE- Local 439, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - UE- Local 441, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - UE- Local 442, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - UE- Local 448, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - UE- Local 451, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - UE- Local 475, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - UE- Local 502, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - UE- Local 506, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - UE- Local 610, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - UE- Local 711, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - UE- Local 724, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - UE- Local 754, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - UE- Local 755, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - UE- Local 768, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - UE- Local 813, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - UE- Local 825, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - UE- Local 902, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - UE- Local 1104, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - UE- Local 1131, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - UE- Local 1150, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - UE- Local 1153, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - UE- Local 1207, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - UE- Local 1225, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - UE- Local 1227, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - UE Locals, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - UE- Lustig, James, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - UE- Matles, James J. Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - UE- Matles, James J. Statements and Speeches, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - UE- McLeish James, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - UE- Membership Bulletin, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - UE- Memorandums to General Officers, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - UE- Mintz, Robert, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - UE- Miscellaneous, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - UE- Money for War, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - UE- Newell, Charles, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - UE- Organizational Gains, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - UE- Organizers' Bulletins, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - UE- Policy, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - UE- Production Awards, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - UE- Production Councils, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - UE- Public Aggairs Guide, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - UE- Public Affairs Guide, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - UE- Publications, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - UE- Radio Script, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - UE News, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - UE News Copy, March 1941 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - UE News Copy, April-June 1941 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - UE News Copy, July-September 1941 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - UE News Copy, October 1941 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - UE News Copy, November 1941 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - UE News Copy, December 1941 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - UE- Publications, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - UE- Press Releases, undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - UE- Senate Briefs, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - UE- Special Releases, undated (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - UE- Staff Files, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - UE- Statistical, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - UE- Union Label, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - UE- Utilities Division, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - UE- "Win the War", 1942 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - UE- Worksheet, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Unemployment, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Unions - General, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Unionists in Armed Forces, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - United Construction Workers, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - United Mine Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - United Press Associations - Washington Bureau, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - United States- Branches of Government, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - United States- Congress, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - United States- Congress, Bills, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - United States- Congress, Dies Committee Bill, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - United States House of Representatives, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - United States House of Representatives HR 2871, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - United States House of Representatives HR 7742, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - United States Senate, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - United States Senate, Norris, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - United States Senate Smaller War Plants Bill, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - United States- Congress, Smith Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - United States- Congress, Truman Committee, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Justice, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Labor, Division of Public Contracts, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Labor, Wage and Hour Division, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - United States- Congress, Economic Stabilization Board, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - United States- Congress, Fiscal Data, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - United States- Government Printing Office, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - United States- Government Printing Office, Division of Public Documents, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - United States- Incomes, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - United States- Information Office, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - United States- Labor Policy, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - United States- Legislation, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - United States- Library of Congress, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - United States- Maritime Commission, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - United States- National Defense, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - United States- National War Labor Board, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - United States- Navy, Bureau of Ordnance, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - United States- Navy, Knox, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - United States- Office of the Attorney General, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - United States- Office of Civilian Defense, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - United States- Office of Emergency Management, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - United States- Office of Facts and Figures, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - United States- Office of Government Reports, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - United States- Office of Price Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - United States- Population, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - United States- Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - United States- Selective Service, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - United States- Treasury Depaartment, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - United States- United States News, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - United States- Wage Hour Division, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - United States- Wallace, Henry A., 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - United States- War Department, Bureau of Public Relations, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - United States- War Production Board, Controlled Materials Plan, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - United States- War Production Board, Nelson, Donald, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - United States- War Production Board, Nelson, Donald, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - United States- War Production Board, Newspaper Advisory Committee, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - United States- War Production Board, Orders Affecting UE's Industry, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - United States- War Production Board, Orders Affecting UE's Industry, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - United States- Ways and Means Committee, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - "U.S. Week", 1941 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Utilities, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Von Kaltenborn, Hans, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Wage and Hour Laws, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Wagner Act, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Wagner, Robert, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Walling, Metcalfe L., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Walsh-Healey Act, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Walsh, Ruth, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - War - Miscellaneous, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Ward, Estlov, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Washington, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Watson, Morris, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Welsh, Patrick J., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Western Electric Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Westinghouse- Brief, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Westinghouse- Miscellaneous, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Westinghouse- UE, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Wheeler, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - White, William Allen, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Wide World Photos, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Willkie, Wendell, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Wilson, Charles, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Wilson, H.W., undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Winn, Frank, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Wishart, Robert, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Witt, Nathan, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - WNEW Radio, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - W olf, Herman, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Women Workers, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Women's International Exposition, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Woodward, Julian L., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - "Work or Fight", 1940 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Workers Education Bureau, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Works Project Administration, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Wright, Fred, undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Wright, Tom, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Wrong, Hume, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Yale University, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Yorty Committee, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Young, Ruth, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - "Your Union At Work", 1940 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Youth Digest, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Zon, Henry, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Nathan Spero, 1937-2001; 10.1.2.
  This subgroup contains various work-related materials of Nat Spero, Research Director for the UE from 1944 to 1983. This collection contains pamphlets and articles on various labor issues that were used as research material for union publications. Also included are letters of correspondence requesting information on a variety of labor related topics and annual reports, as well as work related documents from Spero's time with the Works Progress Administration. Photographs, cards by Fred Wright and research material collected by researcher Jane LaTour are also present.
  - Bibliography, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Letters of Request, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - UE Miscellaneous- UE People, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Photographs (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Frances Perkins and Women Workers, 1944, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Works Progress Administration Records, 1937-1947 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - UE Publications by Spero (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cards by Fred Wright to Spero, 1944, 1970s, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5-8)
  - Lyric to "Reclassification Rag" (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Queens College Sydney Spero Memorial Award, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Background Information on Nathan Spero (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Research on Nathan Spero and Correspondence with UE Archive (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Interview Releases, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The History of Labor in New York State (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Rochester Labor History Map/Guide (Box 6, Item 2)
  - Organize Those Papers! A Labor Activist's Guide to Archives (Box 6, Item 3)